（百利山丘）
(Bailey Downs)
你在那里看什么呢？
What have you got there?
天呐！
God！
巴斯特？
Baxter?
啊！
Ah！
制作：Jack LA＆清水鼻涕泡＆嬛嬛
出品：sPRINKLE良霂字幕组！
变种女狼
Ginger Snaps
那只野兽杀了我们的狗！
He got our dog！
他杀了巴斯特！
He got Baxter！
闭嘴，诺曼！
Shut up, Norman！
这种事情能发生在一个正常女性身上吗？
Can this happen to a normal woman?
巴斯特变成肥料了
Baxter's fertilizer
但是所有人只是站在那儿，盯着看
And everyone's just standing there like staring
为什么他们不去抓住那个野兽？
Why don't they just catch that thing?
死在这种地方真苦逼
How hard could it be in a place full of dead ends?
操！
Fuck！
割腕太娘们儿了...
Wrists are for girls...
我还是割喉吧！
I'm slitting my throat！
你应该直接上吊
You should definitely hang
你在这种地方死简直就是不切实际
Maybe even your final moment is a cliché around here
我们不是，布丽，我们的死法会让他们受惊的
Not ours, B, ours will rock
你是不是认为我们的死法应该只是超越廉价的娱乐？
You don't think our deaths should be a little more than cheap entertainment?
别开我玩笑，别给我打岔
You jazzed me on this, don't wuss out now
当我躺在那儿，每个人都只会盯着我们看而已
It's the idea of everyone staring at me just lying there
我是说，他们是不是只会...嘲笑我们呢？
I mean, what if they just... laugh?
他们会很惊讶的
They'll be in awe
布丽，自杀是“操你”的极限
B, suicide is like the ultimate "fuck you"
这样才是我们嘛
Come on it's so us
我们发过誓的
it's the pact
生还对你已经没什么意义，你当然不怕
See, it's easy for you, you don't care
我们发过誓无论如何都要在一起的
We swore we'd go together, one way or another
那时候我们才8岁
When we were eight
那又怎样？
So?
不管是说好的十六岁后离家出走还是说我们死在这里
Out by sixteen or dead in this scene
都要永远在一起
but together forever
永远在一起
Together forever
一起跟生活抗争
United against life as we know it
我们会死得很壮观，相信我，布丽
Us dead will be the shit, B, trust me
血太多了...
Too much blood...
而且你的内裤露出来了！
And I can see your gonch！
拍就行了！
Just do it！
主演：埃米莉·帕金斯（饰：布丽奇特·菲茨杰拉德）
凯瑟琳·伊莎贝尔（饰：金吉·菲茨杰拉德）
克里斯·莱切（饰：萨姆尔）
耶西·莫斯（饰：杰森·麦卡地）
丹尼尔·哈普顿（饰：特瑞纳·辛克莱）
彼德·克莱汉（饰：韦特老师）
约翰·布尔瓦（饰：彼德）
咪咪·罗杰斯（饰：帕姆尔）
（请让我穿着这身衣服入土，谢谢）
（无可奉告）
NO COMMENT
（虽然这条路很长，但是这条路能带我们逃出地狱，领向光明）
Long is the way that out of hell leads up to light
好了，好了，好了，好了，好了！
Alright, alright, alright, alright, alright！
我真被你们吓坏了
Well, that was completely disturbing, wasn't it?
你们菲茨姐妹的作品实在是...
You know, the Fitzgerald sisters clearly worked very...
天呐！
God！
我是说，我，我...
I mean, I, I...
好变态，我想呕了
I am completely sickened
很变态，不是吗？
Sickened... by that, wasn't I?
嗯？
Hmm?
听着，下课后到我办公室找我，你们俩，一个一个来
Look, see me in the guidance office, after class, you two, separately
我们能再看一遍金吉姐妹们的作品么？
Can we see the ones of Ginger again?
够了！
Enough！
嘿！
Hey！
作业“百利山丘的生活”，下一个轮到谁了？
Life in Bailey Downs, huh? Who's next?
美女们，跑吧！为了你们的炮友！
Oh yes, ladies, run！Run for daddy！
弹起来
Bounce
我打赌那个厉害
I bet she's good to go
你想打赌菲茨姐妹中的一个？
You wanna do a Fitzgerald?
你开玩笑吧？
You're kidding?
白痴，不是那个矮的
Not the little dweeb, you goinks
我是说高的那个！
The one with the rack！
红头发的
The redhead
奇怪，麦卡地好像在偷看我
Odd, I think McCardy just checked me
你很在意吧？
Like you care, right?
高中就像傻逼制造机
High school is just a mindless little breeders machine
完全是荷尔蒙厕所
A total hormonal toilet
我比较愿意做宅女
I'd rather wait it all out in our room
你的背怎么了？
What is with your back?
我也不知道
I don't know
来玩“发现和破坏”吧
Hey, 'Search and Destroy', go
好，就选特瑞纳辛克莱吧
OK, Trina Sinclair
选得好，继续
Excellent selection, continue
特瑞纳·辛克莱，在走廊染发时死的
Trina Sinclair, D.O.A. at the hair dye aisle
她想找发夹，但是只找到减肥药和泻药
Perished while seeking matching barrettes on nothing but diet pills and laxatives
她喜欢把她的短裤弄进屎眼
Likes her shorts stuck up her ass crack
她平时不交作业的借口是：我的指甲油把作业腐蚀了
Favorite homework excuse: my nail glitter ate it
搞笑
Basic pleasure model
标准型只会勾引男人的荡妇
Your standard, cumbuckety date bait
说的好
Good one
-换场地，走吧，同学们  -臭婊子！
-Line change, let's go, girls  -Fucking bitch！
嗷噢？
Uh-oh?
再来一次
Let's do this again
我掩护你
I'll cover you
好
Good
跳起来，宝贝们，跳起来！继续跑！噢，耶！
Bounce, babies, bounce！Keep running！Oh, yeah！
你想赢吧，宝贝
You want it, baby
加油，宝贝！
C'mon, honey！
噢耶，宝贝！
Oh yeah, baby！
你想赢吧，宝贝
You want it baby
滚一边玩蛋去！
Fuck off！
噢！
Oh！
啊哈哈哈！
Ah ha ha ha！
耶！
Yeah！
百利山丘的野兽又袭击了
The Beast of Bailey Downs' strikes again
这是本周的第四条狗了
That's four dogs this week
哇，你中奖了！
Oh! Wow... bonus！
我猜你是用狗来做染发剂的
I guess you're D.O.A. on a dog, huh, Fitz-face?
够了
That's enough
你还好吧？
Are you OK?
太恶心了
Terrific
一条疯狗啊
That is one mother-fucking mad dog
布丽奇特, 去弄干净吧
Brigitte, go get cleaned up
以后少碰我妹妹
Don't ever touch my sister again
有本事搞我啊，变态
Stop me, freak
够了！住手！
Enough！Break it up！
喂，刚才那个门卫往你衣服里面看了
Hey, that janitor was looking right down your shirt
肯定的
Sure
想我去杀了特瑞纳吗？
Want me to kill her?
我为你杀了她，布丽
I'll kill her for you, B
随便
Whatever
不，不能随便，这种事情不能随便
No, not whatever, this isn't whatever
其实，我想虐待她，怎样？
Seriously, what about torture?
你想怎样就怎样吧
Anything you want
好像...
Or...
她有一条狗
she has that dog
我们可以诱拐它，让它死得好像被百利山丘的野兽袭击了一样
We could kidnap it, make it look like he got eaten by 'The Beast of Bailey Downs'
正好上次的作业还剩下一些血没用完
We got all that blood and fake guts from the slide show
好，够邪恶的，就这么决定吧
Yeah, that's wicked, let's do it
她跟毒贩勾搭，她想引起大家对她的注意
She screws a drug dealer, she's begging for negative attention
萨姆，你会给我打电话吗？
So, Sam are you... are you gonna call me?
你有我的电话吧？
OK, you have my number, right?
我之前好像给过你？
Remember when I gave it to you, before?
萨姆
Sam
好吧，再见！
OK, bye！
走吧
Let's get up
真是个傻逼
Such a dickhead
看见没...
See...
你想让白痴离你远点儿
You'd let idiots get away with fucking you up
这就是为什么上帝派我来——
That's why the big Buddha made me——
弄走他们
To stop them
是啊，到现在你可是什么都没干
Yeah, so far you're really kicking ass
给我一个准确的目标
Just give me one clean shot
就一个，我他妈给你保证
Just one, I fucking promise you
别跟我开玩笑！
Don't humor me！
嗯，菲茨...
So, uh, Fitz...
我想我们应该一起走吧
I think we should get together
呃...
Er...
不可以
No
婊子！
Bitch！
跳起来，诺曼，诺曼，跳起来，诺曼，快点
Jump, Norman, Norman, jump, Norman, come on
布丽...
B...
别说你刚才那么做是为了陪我
Just say you won't go average on me
没看见他蠢蠢欲动的样子？
Just 'cause some gonad gets his zipper going?
让我死了算了
Rather be dead
在这儿没有你，我还不如死了
I'd rather die than be here without you
开玩笑，你都还没死，你个傻逼
Relax, you're not, you big suck
金吉, 别推你妹妹
Ginger, don't push your sister
天呐，我讨厌我们的基因链
God, I hate our gene pool
看，孩子们
Look, girls
松口，松口，你把它弄坏了！
Come on, let go, let go, you're ruining it！
金吉，你干吗一直揉你的背？
Ginger, why are you rubbing your back?
痛
It hurts
为什么痛？
Why?
嗯，因为疼痛通过神经反射给大脑
Well, pain flows up your nerve endings to the synapses in your brain
没啥好笑的
She's not funny
怎么弄伤的？
How did you hurt it?
装死的时候
Being dead
是尾骨疼吗，还是再往上一点？
Does it hurt down by your tail bone, or is it up higher?
还是在这一块儿？
Is it tight throughout here?
可能是吧
Maybe
后面疼吗？
Does it ache back here?
可能吧...
Might...
噢，天呐
Oh, my god
你觉得是痛经吧？
Do you think it's cramps?
别说了，好吧？
Give it a rest for two seconds?
帕姆, 我们正在吃饭呢
Pam, we're eating
亨利，你知不知道孩子们三年前就该来月经了？
Henry, the girls are both three years late menstruating, OK?
再不来就不正常了
It's not normal, if it's finally happening...
才不是！
It's not！
亲爱的，没什么可怕的，这很正常
Honey, it's nothing to be scared of, it's the most normal thing in the world
也许是脊椎癌
Maybe it's cancer of the spine
金吉...
Ginger, and...
或者肺结核
Or tuberculosis
看看你这什么态度？
See what your attitude does?
或者脊椎炎
Or spondylitis
脊椎什么？
Spondo what?
脊椎发炎
Fuses your vertebrae together
说得好
Nice
布丽奇特，别说了！
Brigitte, stop it！
不用紧张嘛！
Have a fit！
我受够你们这种腔调了
I've had just about enough of that tone
我们也受够你的腔调了，操！
That makes two of us, fuck！
够了！回你自己的房间！
That's it！To your room！
求之不得
Gladly
布丽奇特，不要被你姐姐带坏了
Brigitte, you are not connected at her wrist
今晚我要和你父亲谈谈，我不希望你离开家门
Your father and I have counseling tonight, I don't want you leaving the house
新闻说野兽还在外面活动
The news says there's still some wild animal on the loose
她们从不出门
They never go out
你总是包庇他们
Well, you're a big help
跟以前一样
As usual
金吉
Ginger
什么事？
What?
我们会被发现的
We'll get caught
不，不会的
No, we won't
那条狗都不会出门
The dog won't even be out
但是它总得出来撒尿
But he has to pee some time
主人不会一直让狗呆在外面
People don't leave their dogs out alone anymore
那你在我把特瑞纳的狗杀掉时把特瑞纳引开
Then you will just have to distract her while I nab the pooch and make with the gore
我可引不了她
I can't distract her
操你啊，布丽，这可是你的主意
The fuck, B, this is your idea
如果你不喜欢你的主意就不要说出来
If you don't like your ideas, stop having them
对不起
Sorry
我已经受够她们了，明白吗？
I've just had it with eating all this shit, OK?
你看
Check it out
我们可以把这只狗带走，她会吓死的
Now we can even leave a body, she'll freak
噢，真恶心
Oh, wicked
拿着他那条...
Take his...
...腿？
leg?
他还是热乎乎的
He's still warm
恶心
Oh, gross
操！
Shit！
别理它了吧，讨厌
Leave it then, the drag
你身上染了血
You got some on you
我操
Nice
什么东西？
What?
布丽...
B...
我来大姨妈了
I just got the curse
呃
Eww
不会传染的！
Well, it's not contagious!
我知道
I know that
天呐！
God！
我是说，死也要死得有个性啊
I mean, kill yourself to be different and your own body screws you
但是如果哪天我开始对着卫生间发呆
But if I start simping around tampon dispensers
...或者因为月经而呻吟，杀了我好吗？
and moaning about PMS, shoot me, OK?
我们快离开这里吧
Let's get out of here
金吉！
Ginger！
金吉？
Ginger?
金吉！
Ginger！
啊！
Ah！
噢，天呐！他还在我后面！
Oh, god！He's right behind me！
啊！
Ah！
噢，我的天呐！
Oh, my god！
啊！
Ah！
金吉！
Ginger！
起来，快点，起来 ！
Get up, come on, get up！
啊！
Ah！
噢，我操！
Oh, fuck me！
该死！
Shit！
妈妈！
Mom！
爸爸！救命！
Dad！Help！
我看看
Let me see
不，好痛，像火烧一样
No, it hurts, it burns
我必须看看，金吉
I have to see, Ginger
好痛
It hurts
那是什么？那是什么？
What was it? What was it?
我不知道，可能是条大狗
I don't know, a big dog, maybe
怎么了？我做了什么？
That's not... what did I do? What...
嘘！
Shh！
我以前见过这东西，好像是熊
I saw this thing once, on bears
听说熊好像会跟在来月经的女孩后面，因为它们闻道味道
Said a bear will like, come after a girl on the rag, because of the smell
我操他妈个逼，那只肯定不是熊！
It wasn't a fucking bear！
他妈个逼的这里不可能会有熊
There wasn't any fucking bears anywhere near here
痛吗？
Does that hurt?
不痛
No
不可能，伤口在愈合！
That's impossible, they're already healing
不，不对劲，我要打911报警
No, this isn't right, I'm calling 911
不要！不要！
No！No！
布丽，我已经不流血了，不是吗？
B, I'm not bleeding anymore, right?
我是说...
I mean...
...我只是不想让妈妈知道，行吧？
Just spare me Pam finding out, OK?
我没事，好吧？
I'm okay, OK?
好吧，我没事
OK, I'm okay
我没事，我没事
I'm okay, I'm okay
我以为你要死了
I thought you were gonna die
我没事
I'm okay
开始攻击健康细胞
Preying upon normal healthy cells
慢慢的吞噬他们
The intruder gradually devours the host from within
最后消耗掉它的宿主
Eventually the invader consumes its host completely
并且完全破坏它
and finally destroys it
缩瞳症包含两条独立完整的序列
Complete meiosis involves two successive division sequences
出现四个新细胞，每个细胞都是单个的
which result in four new cells, each of which is haploid
这种的免费送日历
This one comes with a free calendar
你确定你只是来经了？
Are you sure it's just cramps?
你要知道...
Just so you know...
“只是”和“来经”这两个词不能一起用
The words 'just' and 'cramps', they don't go together
好吧，你真的不再是小女孩了
OK, you're really girling out here
总有一天你也会经历我的痛苦
One day, you too will know my pain
嘿，跟我混吧，我已经有三个小弟了
Hey, diss me or whatever, but I got three sisters...
抽烟可以让人无拘无束
and nothing quite takes the edge off like a good toke
嗯，也许我喜欢我的拘束呢，谢谢你的好意
Well, maybe I like my edge, thanks
也许你只是不敢而已
Or maybe you're just chickened to lose it
把烟拿来
Just pass it, fag
这才是好姑娘
That a girl
是啊！
Yeah！
五十块钱一克
An eighth's fifty
我不想要毒品
I don't want any drugs
那你想干嘛？
Then amscray
我只是在好奇你昨晚撞到了什么
I was just wondering what you hit
好吧，警官，我想我撞了一只狼人
Well, officer, it looked like a lycanthrope to me, sir
我知道什么是狼人
I know what a lycanthrope is
你当然知道
Sure you do
觉得看到狼人有意思么？
Think you see werewolves a lot?
你呢？
Why, do you?
有用吗？
Is it working?
不，我才没兴趣
No, but now I just don't care
你们三个家伙在这里干毛线？
What the hell are you guys doing in here?
萨姆大哥
Sam, the Man
萨姆大哥， 我们只不过是想找个地方抽烟
Sam, man, we just needed a place to come and smoke
嘿，我知道了
Hey, you know, I have an idea.
你他妈的全部给我滚出我的车，混蛋！
Why don't you guys get the fuck out of my van, assholes！
我可是说真的，滚出去！滚出去！滚出去！
No, I'm serious, get out！Get out！Get out！
-萨姆尔，你的车怎么了？  -噢，操！
-Samuel, what happened to your truck?  -Oh, shit！
我撞了棵树，再见
I tapped a tree, all right? Good bye
金吉， 我们走吧
Ginge, let's go
是啊，快去和你那种怪物同类玩吧！
Yeah, why don't you stick to your own species Fitzenstein?
特瑞纳，揍你啊
Trina, stick my fist
噢，你个婊子！
Oh, you bitch！
没事，宝贝
It's OK, baby
金吉， 你是怎么了？
Ginge, what's going on?
你有点不对劲
Something's wrong
你变得越来越...
Like more than you being just...
...女人了
...female
你就说句话好吗？
Can you just say something, please?
哇！
Wow！
“哇”？你就只会说这个？“哇”？
'Wow'? That's it? 'Wow'?
我不要长胸毛啊，布丽
I can't have a hairy chest, B
这真他妈见鬼！
That's fucked！
不可能
No way
不可能个妈逼啊？
The fuck?
他妈逼的有什么不可能？
What the fuck?
这不会是...
This isn't...
什么？
What?
不可能，好像...
No way, like...
什么啊？
What?
满月的时候被咬，然后现在你就长了这么多毛？
Bitten on a full moon, now you're hairy?
我知道，但是你想想
I know, but think about it
好啊，谢谢你这么严肃地对待我那臭悲剧！
Well, thank you for taking my total fucking nightmare so seriously！
嘿？
Huh?
噢，操！
Oh, shit！
我是要死了还是怎样？
What if I'm dying or something?
我们应该去找护士
We gotta see the nurse
我敢肯定你流了很多血，只是来月经而已
I'm sure it seems like a lot of blood, it's a period
但怎么像是...
But really it was like a...
喷泉一样
Geyser
每个人第一次的时候都会紧张
Everyone seems to panic their first time
你们以前都没来过月经，你们多大了？
Neither of you have had a period before and you're how old?
我快16岁了，她刚15岁，她跳过级
I'm almost 16, she just turned 15, she skipped a grade
如果大量出血并且血很粘稠，那说明正常
A thick, syrupy, voluminous discharge is not uncommon
头几天血会流进子宫
The bulk of the uterine lining is shed within the first few days
然后子宫会收缩，把血像水泵一样逼出来
Contractions, cramps, squeeze it out like a pump
三到五天后，就会有鲜红色的血流出来
In three to five days you'll find lighter, bright-red bleeding
等到有褐色或黑褐的血流出来时，就说明差不多结束了
That may turn to a brownish or blackish sludge, which signals the end of the flow
好吧，所以说这些都正常？
OK, so it's all normal?
非常正常！
Very！
接下来的三十年里每二十八天左右就会来一次
Expect it every twenty eight days, give or take, for the next thirty years
很好，谢谢
Great, thanks
那么那些以前不长的毛是怎么回事？还有疼痛？
What about hair that wasn't there before, and pain?
呃，那也是正常的
Mhm, comes with the territory
谢谢
Thank you
我们走吧，布丽
Let's go, B
呃，等一下...
Uh uh, wait...
你们现在还得做一个怀孕和性病检查
You'll have to protect against both pregnancy and STDs now...
出于安全考虑！
Playing safe！
希望是哪些婴儿的腿
Wish this were babies' legs
金吉最喜欢的
Ginger's very favorite
恭喜你，亲爱的
Congratulations, sweetie
你可以向我问任何问题
You know you can ask me anything
你死定了
You're so dead
我没有...
I didn't...
我们的小女孩变成女人了
Our little girl's a young woman now
我啥都没有告诉她
I'd never tell her anything
你可别惹我！
Unless you wanted to piss me off！
我希望你没事
I want you to be okay
我没事啊！我只是来月经了，行吧？
I am！I just... just got my period, okay?
现在我长了些诡异的毛
Now, I've got weird hairs
那又怎样？那只是荷尔蒙的关系
So what? That means I've got hormones
他们可能使我变丑，但是不会使我变成怪物
And they may make me butt-ugly, but they do not make me a monster
你又不是被荷尔蒙咬的
So you got bit by a great big hormone
不是你想的那样，他们根本不存在！
Well not by what you think, they don't exist！
诺曼，你他妈的给我闭嘴！
Norman, shut the fuck up！
也许它是在对着你叫
Maybe he's barking at you
我昨晚变身了吗？
Did I change last night?
对着月亮嚎叫， 大开杀戒，早上再变回来？
Howl at the moon, kill shit and change back this morning?
啊？没有！
Huh? No！
有银弹杀我来阻止这些的发生吗？没有！
Did it take a silver bullet to stop that thing? No！
那只野兽已经被那臭车撞死了
It got killed by a fucking truck
你总是为你不懂的东西而扯火
You always blow off anything you don't get
是啊，因为你就是在胡说八道！
Yeah, when it's bullshit！
你跟那些男生一起吸毒
You're doing drugs with guys
你现在真的很不对劲
Something is definitely wrong with you
嗯，也许你是对的，也许我真的遇上了一只怪物
You know, maybe you're right, maybe I do see a monster
是啊，它有绿色的小眼睛
Yeah, it's got these little green eyes
本来就是，大出血，长毛，跟男生鬼混在一起的又不是我
Oh yeah, like I really wish I was hemorrhaging and hairy and sucking off Jason McCardy
你总是妄想成为我！
Well, you always wanted to be me！
这不是你
Well, this isn't you, so
噢，可怜的布丽！我已经长大了，你却没有！
Oh, poor B！I'm growing up and obviously you're not, huh?
别指望我能阻止你
Well don't let me hold you back or anything
噢，别担心，我才不想你阻止我
Oh, well, don't worry, I won't
世上只有一种生物以残杀为乐，就是狼人
Only one creature on earth destroys for pure pleasure, it's a werewolf
天哪，在这
Oh my god, there it is
恶心死啦！
It's hideous！
啊！
Ah！
你他妈快点出来！我要上厕所！
Get the fuck outta the bathroom！I'm trying to get ready！
金吉？天呐
Ginger? Oh my god
喂，喂，喂！
Hello, hello, hello...
嘿！
Hey！
孩子，有烟吗？
Kid, you got a smoke?
没有
No
那你有火吗？
You got a light then?
谢谢
Oh, thank you
我一整个礼拜都在找你，给我一点时间
I just spent a week of my life looking for you, give me a second
你把这个掉在了我车上
You dropped this in my truck
好吧，我们都看见了，那到底是个什么鬼东西?
OK, we both saw it, what the fuck was it?
那可是你撞的
It's what you hit
嗯！我知道
Hmm！I know
但是那他妈的到底是什么？
But what the fuck was it?
好像是个动物，有毛的，四只脚，我也不知道到底是什么
See, I flattened an animal, furry, all-fours, could be anything
我想会不会是“狼人”？
But here I am, thinking 'lycanthrope'
很疯，是吧？
That's crazy, huh?
我很想弄明白，你能去旅馆找我吗？
Book me into the rubber motel, I'm officially all fucked up, right?
如果你弄不明白呢?
What if you're not?
我想这就是为什么男人要割包皮
Well, that would explain the human circumcised dick,
而你们看到它却要跑
and why you were running for your life from it
呃...我得走了，谢谢你把照片还我
Um... I have to go, thanks for my stuff
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
扯淡，谢谢
Bullshit, thanks
不会吧，嘿，扯淡？
No, hey, bullshit?
你说什么?
What do you say?
发誓你不会说出去
Swear you won't call a freak show
好吧，我发誓
Yeah, I swear
我的身体正在发生变化，尤其满月的时候
I'm changing, like right now and full moons have nothing to do with it
你没开玩笑吧 ?
You're serious?
我总是有银弹穿透我脑袋的幻觉
And everything I look at goes silver bullet, in a gun, to my head, the end
哇
Wow
别搞笑，我是说...
Let's not panic here, I mean...
那东西可是被我的车在路上撞死的
For one, that thing on the road, my van did a pretty good job on it
银弹能有什么用？忘掉好莱坞的规矩吧
Without the benefit of silver bullets, so, let's just forget the Hollywood rules
你不是已经好了么，不然你早变身了
There's got to be a cure, right? Otherwise, there would be a hell of a lot more of them
这个就像感染一样，是由内而外渐渐蔓延的
It's like an infection, it works from the inside out, it's like a virus
生物学，你可以从生物学的角度来看啊
Biology, there's something you can sink your teeth into
这么说的话
So to speak
你说的有道理，好像是真的
You're real, your problem's real, the solution's real
不是在吓人
Not bam, death by morality call
有一次我被感染了，一个女孩跟我说试试用银来净化
Then again when I started piercing shit, I got infections, girl says try pure silver, cleared up like that
古人认为金属可以净化血液
The ancients thought pure metals purified their blood
他们认为蚂蟥也可以
They thought leeches did, too
确实
They do
嗨，你怎么不找条绳子把你跟你的荡妇姐姐绑在一起？
Hey, why don't you get your slut-bitch sister a leash?
真是个变态
What a freak
用条漂亮的小鸟项链相连
Nice bird necklace
金吉，可以和你说句话吗？
Ginger, a word?
说对不起么？
Is it sorry?
不是
No
我们走吧，杰森
Come on Jason, let's go
噢，好
Oh, yes
金吉！金吉！
Ginger！Ginger！
嘿，她要排卵呢！
Hey, she's ovulating！
拜拜咯，疯子
See you, freak
拜拜
Bye bye
月经让你姐又兴奋又困惑
This is a very exciting, confusing time for your sister
孩子，她的身体正在适应这种变化
Boys, her body, trying to fit in
等她习惯了她会跟你多多沟通的
Maybe if she felt that she could share more with you
你们都会变得更加快乐
you'd both be a lot happier
你懂的，布丽奇特，早晚有一天你也会这样
You know, Brigitte, your turn's coming, too, one day
我忍不住了
My stomach
悠着点，好吗？我们有一整晚
Hey, take it easy, all right? We've got all night
不好意思，你让我欲火焚身了
Sorry, you just taste really good
躺好就行了
Just lie back and relax
你才是要躺好的那一个！
You lie back and relax！
谁是男人啊？
Who's the guy here?
谁是男人啊？嘿？哪閪个才是男人啊？
Who's the guy here? Huh? Who's the fucking guy here?
我们要做点保护措施吧？
Don't we need protection here?
住手！
Stop it！
等一下！
Wait a second！
你个可笑的窝囊废
You're fucking hilarious, cave boy
金吉？
Ginger?
发生什么了？
What happened?
麦卡地伤害你了？
Did he hurt you?
如果他伤害你了，你一定要说
If he hurt you, you should tell
哦，我的天呐！
Oh, my god！
滚出去！滚出去！
Get out！Get out！
怎么了？
What happened?
真的是，真的是大事不妙了，布丽
Something is really, really wrong with me, B
发生什么了？
What happened?
我觉得很不舒服...
I get this ache and...
...我原来以为是性饥渴，事实上是我想把所有的东西都撕成碎片
I thought it was for sex, but it's to tear everything into fucking pieces
他在哪儿？
Where is he?
隔壁
Next door
噢，我的天呐！
Oh, my god！
你把诺曼宰了
You killed Norman
他对着我叫了又叫，他妈的一直叫个不停，然后...
He barked and he barked and he kept fucking barking, and...
我只是，我只是...
I just... I just...
阻止不了我自己
I couldn't stop myself
布丽, 我该怎么办？
B, what am I supposed to do?
我真没想到会这样
It wasn't at all like I thought it would be
我满脑子都是他蠕动的情景和他的尖叫声
There was just all this squirming and squealing
所以我就这么把他宰了？
And than he's done, and you're like 'Oh?'
去吧，跟所有的人说我是个变态
Just probably out there telling everyone what a freak I am
他们会认为是他的错
We'll say the same thing about him
并不是你想那样的，我是说，他被我搞了
It doesn't work like that, I mean, he got laid
他是大英雄，我只是一个骚货而已，一个变态
I'm just a lay, he's a hero and I'm just a lay, a freaked mutant lay
你试过什么方法没有？
Did you use something?
没
No
你认为这玩意儿有没有用？
You really think this will work?
我们总得试一下
We have to try something
你从哪儿弄到这个戒指的？
Where did you get that, that ring?
随便找的
I found it
不太好啊
Too bad
我是说，你也该有一个跟我的配对
You should have one too, I mean, for being with me on this
准备好了么？
Ready?
嗯
Yeah
妈的, 卡住了！
Shit, it's stuck！
抓紧了
Hold still
操！快点！
Fuck！Hurry up！
对不起，对不起
Sorry, sorry
快好啦
It's almost there
感觉如何？
How do you feel?
很好
Wicked
诺曼？
Norman?
嗨，诺曼
Hey, Norman
快点！
Hurry up！
别急，已经很快了
Hold still, I am, hurry up
快啊，打，宝贝
Come on, hit it, baby
哦，麦卡地，你怎么了？
Oh, McCardy what happened to you?
金吉菲茨杰拉德颠覆了我的世界
Ginger Fitzgerald rocked my world
怎么，连你的经期也来了？
What, did you get your rag, too?
噢，我操！
Oh, shit！
肯定是墨水，妈的！
It must be ink, all right? Fuck！
嗨！
Hi！
布丽吉特！
Brigitte！
布丽奇特, 过来
Brigitte, come here
你他妈的怎么回事啊，布丽？你有男朋友了？
What the fuck, B? Did you get a boyfriend or something?
不，我们只是...
No, we just...
我一会回来
I'll be right back
我去
Oh my god
嗨，你最近怎样了？
Hey, what's up?
听着，也许银弹好使，我读过一些资料，我有了一个主意
Look, if silver's shot, I've been reading and I got another idea
你吸毒吸得脑残了吧？我现在在上课
Are you on drugs, like right now? I'm in class here
哦，很抱歉骚扰了你
Yeah, excuse me for giving a shit.
我一会再来看你，好吗？
I'll come see you later, OK?
随便
Whatever
菲茨姐妹很抢手嘛
The Fitzen sister are really getting around
好啦，换场地，走吧
OK, line change, let's go
他以为被咬的是我
He thinks I got bit
我那么相信你，你却都告诉了一个陌生人
I trust you, and you blabbed to the first fuck-up who comes along
他懂得一些，他想帮忙
He knows stuff, he wants to help
他想脱你裤子，傻逼！
He wants to get down your pants, stupid！
你们家里有婊子啊，死变态！
So, sluts run in the family... quel shocker！
住手！
Knock it off！
金吉，不！
Ginger, no！
金吉，不！住手！
Ginger, no！Stop！
打, 打, 打...
Fight, fight, fight...
你先引起的，金吉，去办公室
You started it, Ginger, to the office
学校对暴力事件向来是毫不留情的
This school has a 'zero tolerance for violence'-policy
不过看在你的实际情况
I mean a temper like that is inexcusable
我决定从轻发落
barring substantial extenuating circumstances
你看什么呢？哈？
What are you looking at? Huh?
我钢笔漏水了，行了吧？
My pen exploded, OK?
我的红钢笔
My red pen
真他妈不可思议
That was fucking incredible
拿相机出来，你不是有带吗？快点
Get your camera, don't you have a camera? This is wall-worthy, come on
你已经感染了杰森
You gave it to Jason
你们做爱前没做好保护措施，然后你就感染了他
You had unprotected sex, and you infected him
噢！
Oops！
我必须去找萨姆，他有办法
I have to see Sam, he's got an idea
我敢打赌他有办法，那么我们走吧
I bet he does, well, let's go
金吉，如果你要来，最好克制住
If you come, you can't be weird, Ginger
如果他知道我撒谎了，如果他知道你才是...
If he gets I lied, if he gets that you're really the one who's really...
是什么？一只怪物？一个变态？
A what? A monster? Huh, a freak?
如果他知道我骗了他，这事就吹了
If he thinks I dicked him around, he'll blow this off
那我正经点
I'll behave
罗密欧，罗密欧，哪里有亲爱的罗密欧？
Romeo, Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
嘿！
Hey！
刚才的事对不起，我是怕有人听见
Sorry about before, I was just afraid someone would hear us, that's all
嗯，她最近有点神经质
Yeah, she is just a little moody lately
显然那个银戒指没起什么作用，不是么？
That whole silver thing didn't quite work out, did it?
我还没有想过要有另外一个伙伴
I wasn't expecting company
我姐姐，金吉，她知道这事
My sister, Ginger, she knows
如果你俩都要进来，要当做什么没看见，明白吗？
If you two come in here, you see sweet fuck all, understood?
天哪！
Jesus！
霸气，熏得我们都激动起来了
Wicked, smoke us up！
是啊，很霸气啊，你他妈给我出来！
Yeah, wicked huh? Get the fuck out！
嘿，布丽奇特
Hi, Brigitte
我说一下我的看法
It brakes down like this
我比较了一下
I compared
针对感染者的疗法，你看
Homeopathic treatments of infections to the folklore of all this, take a look
乌头草
Aconitum di lycotonum
狼人用的那个？
'Lyco' as in wolf?
是的
Right
它名叫附子草，附子科的，小剂量使用比较安全
It's called Monkshood, it's a cousin of wolfsbane, except this stuff is safe in small doses
有超强的自我解毒效果
It's a super oxidant breed, radical detox
能促进白细胞繁殖
It promotes white blood cell growth
来对抗感染，你有这种草么
Which fight infection, do you have some?
它是多年生草本，到处都长，但是只有春天有
Well, it's perennial, it grows everywhere, but only in the spring
操，纯扯淡，好吧？
Fuck！This is bullshit, OK?
我播了种，还在长
I seeded some, I'm growing it
她没时间了
She doesn't have time for that
她已经杀了一条狗了，她完蛋了
She's killed a dog already, she's fucked
她都长尾巴了，你告诉过他么?
She's growing a tail, did you tell him that?
金吉！
Ginger！
你长尾巴了？
You're growing a tail?
是的
Yes
看，他不过是一个只会打飞机的小子，好吧？
Look, he's just another wank job, OK?
你他妈以为你是谁啊？把书给我
What the fuck do you think you are? Give me that
你他妈的你又是谁，变态，她才15岁！
What the fuck are you? Pervert, she's 15！
金吉，出去等着
Ginger, wait outside！
好，如果他强暴你，别哭着回来，我随时在家
Fine, if he rapes you, don't come crying, I'll be at home
她刚刚在发神经
She's just freaking
我不会把你想的跟她一样
I do not think of you that way
操！操！操！
Fuck！Fuck！Fuck！
你爸电池又没电了，我得去趟超市
Your dad's battery is dead again, he's stranded at the supermarket
想去兜风吗？
Wanna go for a ride?
操你啊，你就不会敲门么？
Jesus, can't you knock?
别说“操”我
Don't you 'Jesus' me
你身上有什么是我没见过的
You don't have anything I haven't seen before
那只是你自己那么认为
That's what you think
什么意思？
What is that supposed to mean?
没什么，我只是变胖了，好了，你出去吧
Nothing, I'm just, I'm fat, all right, get out
金吉，你不胖， 你的身材就跟模特一样火辣
Ginger, you are not fat, these fashion models are all on speed to look like that
出去！
Get out！
好吧，天呐
OK, gosh
我一会回来
I'll be back soon
把狗还给我
Give me back my dog
特瑞纳，你的狗不在我这儿
Trina, I don't have your dog
金吉把它带走了，我看见了
Ginger took him, I saw her
我对你感到遗憾的是，他是不可能喜欢你的
You know, I feel sorry for you,  he doesn't like you.
他是只难得的猎狗，还没交配过
He's a cherry-hound, he's into virgins
特瑞纳，你好烦，回家吧
Trina, you're bleeding, go home.
你如果真他妈识相点，你就会知道你是满足不了它的
If you are so fucking smart, you won't give him the satisfaction
以前就有人想带走它，却不能满足它！
Somebody just once shouldn't give that fucker the satisfaction！
特瑞纳，走吧
Trina, go now
你跟你姐一样都是婊子
You are as big a cunt as your sister
我不是
I am not
嗨，胖妞儿，还想回来挨更多的揍吗？
Hey, meat, back for more?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我不知道，布丽，我在干嘛？打给萨姆，问问专家
I don't know, B, what am I doing? Call Sam, ask the pro
啥？
What?
你跟你的新朋友玩，我也有我的
You play with your new friends,  and I'll play with mine
金吉，你他妈的到底在干什么？
Ginger, what the hell are you doing?
你闻起来很香啊，是什么味道呢？
You smell yummy, what is that?
柠檬？还是杀虫剂？我不知道
Citrus or antiseptic? I'm not sure
你疯了吗？
Are you crazy?
够了，放了她吧
OK, that's enough, just let her go
闭嘴，闭嘴，闭嘴
Shut up, shut up, shut up
特瑞纳，你冷静点，行不？
OK, let's just chill, right, Trina?
你知道吗，特瑞纳？她在让我放了你，也许她想跟你做朋友
You know what, Trina? She's doing your boy, now, I wouldn't be so quick to get so friendly
够了，不是那回事
Stop it, it's not like that
我想她被你吓坏了吧，亲，是吗？
I think she's scared for you, love, huh?
她是个混蛋，不值得你这样
She's an asshole, she's not worth it
这都是因为你！
You asked for this！
你有了萨姆忘了我，不管现在发生了什么都是你的错！
You picked Sam over me, whatever happens now, it is your fault！
这不是你，我们想想办法
This is not you, just let's cope
有啥办法？就靠这种没用的垃圾？
Oh, with... with what? With this kind of shit？
他错了，傻逼，这东西没用！
He's wrong, moron, you can't fix this!
你不懂，给我个机会试一试啊
You don't know that, just give me a chance
试什么，别的办法？天呐，我不懂啊，布丽...
What, another one? God gee, I don't know, B...
你看，我正离你越来越远...
See I'm going way way out there...
我离你那烂世界烂规矩越来越远
Way way far from where you live, which you pretty much fucking rule
噢，天呐，你这臭女人太恶心了，真是太他妈...
Oh god, that's disgusting, you fucking gross, fucking...
别过来！别碰我，你们两个变态！你们简直是变态至极！
Back！Don't touch me, you freaks！You're both just totally fucked！
特瑞纳，我们只不过是...
Trina, we were just...
哦哦？
Uh-oh？
快打扮好！
Get up！
Get up now！
亨利，你到底在外面磨叽啥呢？
Henry, what on earth are you doing out there?
快点吧，进来再吃
Come on, don't eat it until we get inside
我的天呐，这是...
Jesus Christ on a bicycle！What the...
孩子们，我说过，不准再在屋子里玩死亡游戏！
Girls, I told you, no more deaths in the house！
冷静，这是最后一次
Don't be mad, it's for extra credit
十分钟之内给我收拾干净
Back to immaculate in ten minutes
玉米糖浆，爸爸，想尝尝么？
Corn syrup, dad, d'you want some?
我把肉冰起来
Well, I better get this meat away
我来
I'll do that.
妈
Mom.
干啥
What?
小伙子们都喜欢啥？
What do guys want?
布丽奇特, 我很高兴你问我这个
Brigitte, I'm so glad you asked
这就是男人想要的
And that's what men want
有的男孩看起来或许很装逼或很与众不同，不过还是很平凡
Some of them might seem cool or different,  but they're all pretty much the same
差不多吧
Totally
感谢分享
Thanks for sharing
噢，亲，我们就是来讨论的嘛
Oh, honey, that's what we're here for
是时候睡觉了，明天还要上学，好好休息吧！
Bed time, it's a school night, beauty rest！
冻上了
This is just great
恩，像曲棍球一样
Yeah, field hockey will suck now
给我找把改锥
Get me a screwdriver
天呐！
Oh, god！
继续吧
Way to go
看这个，《为何你女儿跟傻逼相处？》
Here it is: 'Why your daughter dates dummies?'
很高兴我还保存着
I'm so glad I hung on to this
我觉得她们有点不对劲
I think they're up to something
青春期综合症而已
They're just being normal teenage girls
为啥她们突然对你说的话那么感兴趣了？
Then why are they suddenly so interested in what you have to say?
你就在呆在你那小世界里吧，亨利，这事儿你可想不明白
Stay in your own little world, Henry, this one just confuses you
妈的，这么多蚯蚓
Shit, look at all the worms
还记得我小时候总让你来这里吃蚯蚓么？
Remember when I used to make you eat them just to get in here?
坟墓有点浅？差不多了吧
Shallow grave? Oh well, seems appropriate
你来挖会儿
You dig for a while
听着
Look
没人会认为俩小孩是杀人犯的
Mo one ever thinks chicks do shit like this
相信我，一个女孩只能是个妓女...
Trust me, a girl can only be a slut...
...婊子，荡妇，或是隔壁的处女
...a bitch, a tease, or the virgin next door
我们照常过日子就好了
We'll just coast on how the world works
你觉得她漂亮吗？
Think she's pretty?
如果我不在这儿，你会吃了她吗？
If I wasn't here, would you eat her?
不会
No
我只是想干她
God, that'd be like, fucking her
你以后不能再出去了
You can't go out anymore
我不能宅在家里，我会发疯的
Well, I can't stay in, I'll go mental
我们要让妈妈以为你在学校
We'll make Pam think you're at school
让学校以为你生病在家
We'll make school think you're home sick
确保他们不产生任何怀疑
Just till there is no doubt about us in this
然后我们就消失，离这儿越远越好
Then we blow, as far away from here as possible
请注意
Your attention, please
以下同学请去办公室
Starting immediately certain students will be paged to the office
协助警方调查特瑞纳的失踪案
to assist the police regarding Trina Sinclair's disappearance
她死了，伙计
She is dead, man
当点到你的名字时，请去办公室
When your name is called, please come to the office
（金吉今日因病请假）
啊！
Ah！
金吉正躲着我，是吧？
Is Ginger avoiding me?
我现在感觉很糟
'Cause I'm feeling pretty good right now
我有几个问题想问她
I just got a few questions for her
比如说为什么我屁股上正长出一条尾巴
Like uh...  I'm growing a goddamn tail outta my ass
我想她应该有办法处理，知道怎么把这事儿保密！
And I thought she might have a few tips on how to deal with keeping that quiet！
你伤害我也没什么用，明白吗？
Hurting me won't help, see?
我现在真想那么做
I'm up to some whack shit right now
我快变成魔鬼了
I'm way out on the corner of 'Fucked-Up and Evil'
你知道我昨晚做了什么来取乐么？
You wanna know what I did for fun last night, huh?
我杀了自己的狗，我怎么会做出那种事？
I killed my own freaking dog, OK?  What am I supposed to do about that?
你这次惨透了
You're gonna be in deep shit
我是被你们害惨了
I'm right with you on deep shit
我想你知道这是为什么
And I think you know why
你们在这里干嘛？
What's going on here?
谢谢
Thanks
金吉，今天在学校怎么样？
Ginger, how was school today?
不知道，我没去
I don't know, I didn't go
我们去郊游了
We had a field trip
真的吗？
Really?
我怎么一点也不知道
I didn't sign any form for a field trip
爸，今晚教我们开车好吗？
Daddy, will you teach me how to drive tonight?
也许明年再教吧
Next year, maybe
那么你们说，你们去哪儿了
So where did you go?
如果不会有明年呢？
What if next year never comes?
金吉
Ginger
韦恩老师打电话来了，问你好点儿没
Mr. Wayne called today, he wanted to know if you were feeling any better
还有你什么时候能回去上学
When you might be coming back to school
警察想跟你谈谈关于跟你打过架的失踪的女孩的事
The police wanna talk to you, something about a fight with a missing girl
爸，我可以走了吗？
Daddy, may I be excused?
不，你不可以
No, you may not
金吉，等等
Ginger, wait
干嘛，布丽？
For what, B?
噢，你别走
Oh no, you don't
我想知道怎么回事，就现在
I want to know what's going on, right now
这是什么？
What are these?
附子草，布丽奇特...
Monkshood, Brigitte...
你从哪儿得到的？
Where did you get them?
一家工艺品店买的，现在回答我的问题
From a craft store, now, I want an answer
特瑞纳辛克莱想打我，因为杰森麦卡地更喜欢我们
Trina Sinclair tried to beat me up, 'cause Jason McCardy liked us better
所以金吉就揍了她一顿，就这些
So Ginger beat her up, that's all
就这些？
That's all?
打架？逃学？
Beating up other girls? Cutting classes?
我很失望，布丽奇特
I'm very disappointed, Brigitte
对不起
Sorry
她让你干嘛你就干嘛，你总是这样
You just do whatever she wants you to, you always have
我真希望你能多为自己考虑一下
I really wish you'd start thinking more for yourself
你认为我应该跟她谈谈吗？
Do you think I should talk to her?
当面对质？
Check in?
她觉得你很酷，总是给我们充分的自由来处理自己的事情
She thinks it's cool you let us figure stuff out for ourselves
哦？
Oh?
真的吗？
Really?
我担心这么做对不对
I wondered if that approach was working
你看看妈妈有什么
Look what Pamela had
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
我只是把它切下来而已！
I'll just take it off！
住手！
Stop！
我只是把它切下来而已！
I'll just take it off！
住手！
Stop！
不要！
No！
那些狗是我杀的，只有将活物撕成碎片才能让我好受些
I killed their pets, B, and nothing helps except tearing live things to pieces
我不能再这样了
I can't be like this
这是附子草，我们明天要做的第一件事就是研究下怎么使用
This is monkshood, first thing tomorrow we find out how to use it and we take off
如果你现在放弃了，就是丢下我一个人了
If you give up now, you leave me here alone
我绝不会对你做出这种事！
I would never do that to you！
对不起，我只是很害怕
I'm sorry, I'm scared
（BCX广播台祝你万圣节快乐...）
(BCX radio wishes you a happy Halloween...)
布丽，你他妈的在搞什么？
B, what the fuck are you doing?
嘿，布丽，放我出去！
Hey, B, let me out！
我必须找到治疗你的方法
I have to deal with the cure
只有把你关起来你才不会伤害自己和别人
This way, you can't hurt yourself or anybody else
操你妈，你个死人娘娘腔，是不是要背叛我？
Fuck, you fucking sissy little girl, are you going rat me out?
闭嘴，等着我
Just shut up and wait for me
你个小婊子！操你妈！我恨你！
You little bitch！Fuck you！I hate you！
布丽，放我出去，快点
B, let me out, come on
布丽？
B?
布丽！
B！
放我出去！
Let me out！
天呐，这是附子草，你究竟从哪儿弄来的？
Holy shit, that's monkshood, where the fuck did you get that?
我不知道是烟熏还是吃掉还是怎样，但是我必须马上试试
I don't know if you smoke it or eat it or what, but I need to try it now
虽然你拿来了，但是...
Well, you got me but...
我直说吧，最好是注射
To be sure, I'd have to say direct route, inject it
但是，这不是个好办法，因为没人知道这东西有没有用
But see, that's a bad idea, Brigitte, because neither of us know what this stuff does
总不会比做马路杀手更糟糕
It can't be worse than being road kill
这种方法也只不过是猜测，我是说...
The dosage will be a guess, I mean...
用法用量都不清楚，而且可能有副作用
It would have to be, there is no way to match for metabolism, body weight, there could be side effects
你不能一个人试
You can not try this alone
我姐姐会陪我
My sister will be there
你得知道救她可能会杀死她
Understand you may kill her trying to save her
你说什么？
What?
这是给金吉准备的，不是吗？
It's for Ginger, isn't it?
最坏的结果是，她永远解脱了
Look, worst-case scenario, you put her out of her misery
只要你有十足的心理准备就行
Just as long as you're prepared for that, and I mean sure
今晚再来吧
Try to come tonight
嘿，你们见到杰森了吗？
Hey, have you seen Jason?
呃...你头上有点...
Umm... you got a little...
你们今晚会去温室派对吗？
You're going to the greenhouse bash tonight?
嗯，是啊
Erm, yeah
好
Good
今晚我负责奖品，你们都可以赢到
I'm in charge of the prizes, you, too, could be winner
金吉，到我办公室来，现在！
Ginger, my office, now！
救命，救命！
Help！Help！
放开我
Let me go
放开我！
Let me go！
放开他，麦卡地
Let him go, McCardy
哦，来了一个少女，很好
Oh yeah, a chick, excellent
来爸爸这里，宝贝
Come to papa, baby
过来给你吃糖
Come and get some candy
我得走了，呃...
I have to go, um...
我还有课
I have a class
请注意
Attention please
布丽奇特菲茨杰拉德请到办公室来一下
Brigitte Fitzgerald, please report to guidance
布丽奇特菲茨杰拉德到办公室来
Brigitte Fitzerald to guidance
布丽，他又想给臭妈妈打电话，告诉她我们需要帮助
He wanted to call fucking Pamela, B, and tell her we needed help
所以我杀了他，看，多管用？我怎么样做才叫背叛你呢？
So, I stopped him, you see how that works? How I do not betray you?
我没背叛你
I didn't betray you
你把我锁了起来
You locked me up
你需要被关起来
You need to get this fixed
为什么啊？所以说我是不是该去监狱度过余生？
Why? So I can go to jail, for the rest... for the rest of my life?
我们等别人走了再说
We wait till everyone leaves
不管怎样，先把这儿清理了
Then we clean this up, somehow
我觉得你现在真是糟透了
I think you've fucked up enough
噢，天呐！
Oh my god！
亨利？
Henry?
噢，天...
Oh, g...
是什么啊？
What is it?
亨利，怕什么，这只是她们的死亡游戏用的道具吧
Henry, for Pete's sake, it's only the girls' death project
都是假的，傻瓜
They're fake, you big baby
我要找东西把这收拾一下
I'm gonna find something to clean this up
呆在这里，把门锁上
Stay here and lock the door
噢，天呐！
Oh, my god！
你好啊，布丽奇特
Hello, Brigitte
住手！
Stop it！
我可以摸一下你的咪咪吗？
Can I touch your boobies?
我喜欢小女孩的咪咪
I like little girls'
放开他！
Leave him alone！
金吉，住手！快住手！
Ginger, Stop！Stop！
金吉，你妈的，快住手！
Ginger, fucking stop！
求你住手！
Please stop！
金吉，住手！他什么都没做！
Ginger, stop！He hasn't done anything！
我不喜欢他看你的眼神
I don't like how he looks at you
噢，天呐！
Oh my god！
他发现我了，布丽奇特
He found me, Brigitte
情急之下，我只能...
The mess, I had to...
去死吧！
Go to hell！
他还没死，但是被你感染了
He's not dead, you've infected him
我们找人帮忙救他吧
Let me call help for him
噢，操！
Oh fuck！
操！
Fuck！
你喜欢这样
You like it
好爽啊，布丽奇特
It feels so... good, Brigitte
好像在碰自己一样
It's like touching yourself
怎么碰都能碰到全身各处
You know every move... right on the fucking dot
之后...
And after...
感觉到火花四射，天旋地转
You see fucking fireworks, supernovas
我就是大自然的王
I'm a goddamn force of nature
我感觉我自己无所不能
I feel like I could do just about anything
你知道，我们不会再像以前那么亲密了
You know we're almost not even related anymore
你他妈个逼啊！
You're fucked！
你会习惯的，我们做做爱，磨磨擦，互喝肉汁
You'd love it, should come for the ride, a little scratch, swap some juice
我们还会在一起，就像以前那样，这么接近，布丽
We'll be our own pack, like before, it's so us, B
我宁愿死也不愿变成你这样
I'd rather be dead than be what you are
我们发过誓的！
We have a pact！
不管是说好的16岁后离家出走还是说某天我们要死在这里
Out by sixteen or dead in this scene,
也要永远地在一起！
but together for fucking ever！
我说过我可以为你死！
I said I would die for you！
不，你说你会和我一起死，因为你没有更好的事做了
No. You said you'd die with me, 'cause you had nothing better to do
操你妈
Fuck you too
你认为我还愿意像以前那么平凡吗？
You think I wanna go back to being nobody?
你死定了！
You're fucked！
别挡我的道，布丽奇特
Stay the hell out of my way, Brigitte
我要去跟萨姆打个招呼
And I'll tell Sam you said hi
停一下！停一下！
Stop！Stop！
你姐姐呢？
Where is your sister?
去酒会了
County greenhouse
上车吧
Get in the van
菲茨，你这打扮真怪异啊，宝贝！
All right, Fitz, wicked costume, baby！
萨姆在哪儿？
Where is Sam?
妈的！
Shit！
嘿
Hey
嘿，金吉，布丽奇特在哪儿？
Hey, Ginger, where is Brigitte?
她不会来了
She couldn't make it
好吧，为啥？
Yeah, why is that?
痛经
Cramps
她让我跟你打招呼
She says hi
你想买东西还是干点别的
You wanna buy or something?
干点别的
something
去把你姐找回来
Go get your sister
妈，我不认为
Mom, I don't think...
你们干了件很可怕的事
You've done a terrible thing
但是...
But...
你们是我的孩子
you're my tiny babies
你们要离开也很正常，我真不愿意你们离开我
It's one thing if you leave, it's almost normal, but no one is gonna take you from me
明天我会把这里洒满汽油放火烧掉
First thing tomorrow I'll let the house fill up with gas, and light a match
什么?
What?
我们再重新开始，为了我的女儿，只能这样了
We'll start fresh  Just us girls  It'll be fun
爸爸那边怎么办
What about dad?
他只会责备我几句而已，他们都会说我的
He'll just blame me, they all will
这不是你的错，妈妈
This isn't your fault, mom
是我的错
Yes it is
关上门
Lock the doors, OK?
金吉，别这样
Ginger, come on
你才别这样
No, you come on
你这是在干嘛 ?
What are you doing?
我知道你想要，每个人都想
I know you want to  Everybody does
你喜欢什么样的?
Really, what would I be like?
我该怎么做 ?
What would I do?
我心里怎么想你知道吗?
What would I feel like inside?
金吉，住手
Ginger, stop
占有我
Make me.
金吉，你妹妹...
Ginger, your sister...
这太见鬼了
This is fucked
金吉，离我远点!
Ginger, get off me. Get off me. Ginger, get off me!
你混蛋!
Jerk!
我告诉过你住手了
What? I told you to stop. Oh Jesus
对不起，金吉，起来
God, Ginger get up. I'm sorry
起来, 金吉.
Get up, Ginger
你个婊子，你想要我？你想要我？别伤害别人了，带我走！
You bitch! You want me? You want me?  Stop hurting everybody else and take me. Take me!
我不想要你，我都不知道你怎么想的
I don't want you! I don't even know you!
布丽奇特，别这样
Brigitte, don't
布丽奇特，别这样!
Brigitte, don't!
你把我周围跟你无关的一切都毁了
You wrecked everything for me that isn't about you
不要，该死
No, Shit
现在，我跟你一样了
Now I am you
我知道，但是我又是什么呢？
I know you are  But what am I?
我们得走了
We got to go
布丽，我走不了, 我变异的太快了
B, I can't  I'm turning too fast
你搞什么？
What the hell did you do that for?
我不能让你跟她走，布丽奇特
I won't let you do this, Brigitte
你们都需要治疗
You both need help
你个傻逼！
You fucking idiot!
解毒剂管用了，我在别人身上用过，我只有回家才能找到更多
The cure works. I had to use it on somebody else, but there is more at the house
我只有这么做才能让她跟我一起回家
This is the only way I could get her to come back with me
天呐!
Oh shit!
我怎么知道?
What? How was I supposed to know that?
帮我，好吗? 把她弄进你的车里跟我们回家
Just help me, OK? Just get her in your truck and drive us home
好吧，把她放在后面
Fine, but she rides in the back
真该死，你应该看看医生
This is nuts, you need a doctor
噢!
Oh!
天呐
Jesus
她会杀了你的，布里奇特
She could have killed you, Brigitte
她需要我
She needs me
到家，把她和我都治好
Get home  Cure her, cure me
然后呢?
And then what?
离开这里
Run
你在拿自己开玩笑
You know you're kidding yourself
我一会回来，把注射器给我
I'll be right back.  Give me the syringe
爸爸？
Dad? Hello?
天呐!
Oh shit!
我去看看
Yeah, I've meant to fix that
她跑了？
Did she get out?
希望没有
Oh god, I hope not
我什么也看不见
I can't see anything
把手电筒给我
Pass me that flashlight
操 !
Fuck!
这就是你的混蛋姐姐
That was your god damn sister!
妈的
Oh fuck
附子草在那儿
The monkshood's in there
你正在失去意识
Oh, you're out of your mind
还好
Not yet
安静，我去拿
Be quiet. I gotta get this stuff
好
Great
妈的，她到底在哪儿?
Fuck! Where the fuck is she?
闭嘴
Shh
快点
Let's do this fast
好
Hell, yes
碗
All right, bowls
酒精
Alcohol, alcohol
布丽奇特...
Brigitte...
...有火 ?
Could I have your lighter?
我的手没感觉了
I can't feel my hand
上帝
Jesus Christ
噢，不 !
Oh fuck!
快跑！快跑!
Go! Go!
酒精
Alcohol
什么？
What?
酒精
Alcohol
太好了
Oh shit  Yeah
把花碾碎
Start grinding up the buds
放进去
All right, pour it in
慢点，慢点
Easy, easy, easy...
什么声音？
What was that?
别管了，继续
Shit, keep going. Go, go
我来弄
All right, hold this
这样很不卫生
Right, that's real fucking hygienic
没关系
I doubt it matters
先把你姐姐打昏怎么样
How about you take this and we blow?
不
How about no?
我来做，你都动不了了
Then let me do it, you can hardly move
不!
No!
你自己不行
You can't do this by yourself
我拿着针，进去
Let me take the needle, I'll go into the living room
你把她引过来，注射，我们就完成了
you lead her in, bam we're done
好
OK
我走了
I'm going
小心点
Be careful
萨姆?
Sam?
金吉?
Ginger?
我不能
I can't
我不愿意
I won't
该死 !
The fuck！
走开 !
Fuck off！
离我远点 !
Leave me alone!
金吉?
Ginger?
是我啊
Come on. It's me
好吧?
OK?
金吉，拜托，是我啊 !
Ginger, please, it's me!
你想要这个 ?
You want this?
我不会跟你死在这间屋子里 !
I'm not dying in this room with you!
我不会死的 !
I'm not dying!
中文字幕：左耳失明